<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on DavidCraddockAudio.com</title>
    <link>https://davidcraddockaudio.com/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on DavidCraddockAudio.com</description>
    <image>
      <title>DavidCraddockAudio.com</title>
      <url>https://davidcraddockaudio.com/mugshot.png</url>
      <link>https://davidcraddockaudio.com/mugshot.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.131.0</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>David Paul Craddock</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 18:46:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://davidcraddockaudio.com/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DJing</title>
      <link>https://davidcraddockaudio.com/DJing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 18:46:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidcraddockaudio.com/DJing/</guid>
      <description>Currently as of 25/5/25: I am DJing every Friday at around 11pm time on Heavy Resistance Aberdeen which is a rock and metal Twitch DJ Stream, with Mark Chalmers and friends.
I&amp;rsquo;m an experienced professional multi-genre DJ. I have excellent technical skills, good creative mixing skills including extensive use of stems and live mashups, combined with a strong ability to read the crowd and a deep and diverse music knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Education</title>
      <link>https://davidcraddockaudio.com/Education/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 18:46:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidcraddockaudio.com/Education/</guid>
      <description>Music Education In tandem with decades of professional experience in DJing and production, I&amp;rsquo;m a firm believer in life-long music education, and have complimented my music work with a lot of formal and informal music education:
I have studied 5 modules in music production and sound engineering focused on DJing and electronic music, one at Canterbury College, one at Manchester School of Electronic Music, and three of which have been at the internationally recognised music school: Point Blank Music School.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Music and Sound Engineering</title>
      <link>https://davidcraddockaudio.com/Engineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 18:46:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidcraddockaudio.com/Engineering/</guid>
      <description>I have a strong music and sound engineering technical element to my skillset, having built several novel DJ set-ups, several music studio builds, including dealing with acoustic challenges, digital streaming challenges, and have built my own modular synthesisers which included extensive research.
My career in IT, software and as a technologist heavily intersects with this, for example: I spent 6 months in BBC R&amp;amp;D&amp;rsquo;s music department working on modelling binaural acoustic research algorithms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Music Production</title>
      <link>https://davidcraddockaudio.com/Production/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 18:46:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://davidcraddockaudio.com/Production/</guid>
      <description> Output I have professionally composed, produced, mixed and mastered two albums, one single, and have released an EP with a collaborator.
Production Examples: A single from my Socialist Synthesis ambient experimental project called ‘Rust Marks’ Remastering the Industrial Comedy classic ‘KOMPRESOR – KOMPRESSOR DOES NOT DANCE’ Production and mixing on the electronica EP &amp;lsquo;Unfinished Dreams&amp;rsquo; as &amp;lsquo;Machines Move Mountains&amp;rsquo; with collaborator Ellis Breen. </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
