<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>DavidCraddock.Games</title>
    <link>https://davidcraddock.games/</link>
    <description>Recent content on DavidCraddock.Games</description>
    <image>
      <title>DavidCraddock.Games</title>
      <url>https://davidcraddock.games/mugshot.png</url>
      <link>https://davidcraddock.games/mugshot.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.131.0</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>David Paul Craddock</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 00:40:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://davidcraddock.games/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Budget Retro Arcade Setup</title>
      <link>https://davidcraddock.games/arcade-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 00:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
       <guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.davidcraddock.games/arcade-setup</guid> 
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always wanted an arcade machine in my home. But I could never really afford one, in terms of time and space.
Recently I thought to myself, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m 42, I&amp;rsquo;m not getting any younger&amp;rdquo;. So I built an arcade setup using the things I already had in the home.
Games The ROMs I have are all stored on my file server upstairs. I can get around a 3gbits/sec connection via my 10gbits/sec home network, so there is no performance &amp;lsquo;hit&amp;rsquo; in streaming them off the network drive - it has similar speed and latency to a physical drive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Gaming Blog</title>
      <link>https://davidcraddock.games/new-gaming-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 00:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
       <guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.davidcraddock.games/?p=1</guid> 
      <description>This is my new gaming blog, where I will write reviews of games I&amp;rsquo;ve played, game accessories I&amp;rsquo;ve bought, and anything else PC or console gaming-related that I can think of.
It is using the same setup as my main https://davidcraddock.net blog - as in - it&amp;rsquo;s self-hosted, and uses the Hugo Go-based static blogging engine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Time Crisis 2 Setup</title>
      <link>https://davidcraddock.games/time-crisis-2-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 00:40:14 +0000</pubDate>
       <guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.davidcraddock.games/?p=2</guid> 
      <description>Time Crisis 2 is a light-gun shooter arcade game developed and published by Namco. It was released in arcades in 1997, and later ported to the PlayStation 2 in 2001. It is the second instalment in the Time Crisis series.
The game features a two-player mode, where each player takes turns using a light gun to shoot enemies and reload. Players can duck behind cover to avoid enemy fire, and pop out to shoot enemies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dragon Age: Veilguard - First Impressions</title>
      <link>https://davidcraddock.games/dragon-age-veilguard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
       <guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.davidcraddock.games/?p=3</guid> 
      <description>I pre-ordered Dragon Age: Veilguard, and started playing it as soon as it downloaded after release.
First impressions? Quite positive! Some initial thoughts:
I&amp;rsquo;ve been a long-time BioWare fan since Baldur&amp;rsquo;s Gate, but was massively disappointed with Mass Effect: Andromeda, so much so that I didn&amp;rsquo;t even bother playing Anthem. I do like the setting and the characterisations in the Dragon Age series, and thought it was worth pre-ordering this game just in case they didn&amp;rsquo;t totally mess it up.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
